{
  "listado": [
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "life of pi",
      "pregunta": "1",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "doctor|dolittle",
      "pregunta": "2",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Psycho",
      "pregunta": "3",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "apollo 13",
      "pregunta": "4",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "kung fu|panda",
      "pregunta": "5",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "eat pray love",
      "pregunta": "6",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Blood|Diamond",
      "pregunta": "7",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "et",
      "pregunta": "8",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "american pie",
      "pregunta": "9",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "men in black",
      "pregunta": "10",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "free willy",
      "pregunta": "11",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "up",
      "pregunta": "12",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Planet of|the Apes",
      "pregunta": "13",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "American|Beauty",
      "pregunta": "14",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "the|lion king",
      "pregunta": "15",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Gorillas in|the Mist",
      "pregunta": "16",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "The Devil|Wears Prada",
      "pregunta": "17",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "x men",
      "pregunta": "18",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "harry potter",
      "pregunta": "19",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "spiderman",
      "pregunta": "20",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Finding|Nemo",
      "pregunta": "21",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "mary poppins",
      "pregunta": "22",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "The Hunger|Games",
      "pregunta": "23",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Fast and|Furious",
      "pregunta": "24",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "cars",
      "pregunta": "25",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "The King|Speak",
      "pregunta": "2626",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "500 Days|of Summer",
      "pregunta": "27",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "angels|and demons",
      "pregunta": "28",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Crocodile|Dundee",
      "pregunta": "29",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "jaws",
      "pregunta": "30",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "sharknado",
      "pregunta": "31",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Lady and|the Tramp",
      "pregunta": "32",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Home Alone",
      "pregunta": "33",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "rambo",
      "pregunta": "34",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Speed",
      "pregunta": "35",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Puss in|Boots",
      "pregunta": "36",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "indiana|jones",
      "pregunta": "37",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "pinocchio",
      "pregunta": "38",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Ghostbusters",
      "pregunta": "39",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "ice age",
      "pregunta": "40",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "scary|movie",
      "pregunta": "41",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "pearl|harbor",
      "pregunta": "42",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "The Butterfly|Effect",
      "pregunta": "43",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "forrest|gump",
      "pregunta": "44",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "The Motorcycle|Diaries",
      "pregunta": "45",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "volcano",
      "pregunta": "46",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Armageddon",
      "pregunta": "47",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "The Scorpion|King",
      "pregunta": "48",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "The Ring",
      "pregunta": "49",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "gravity",
      "pregunta": "50",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "12 Monkeys",
      "pregunta": "51",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Ratatouille",
      "pregunta": "52",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "127 Hours",
      "pregunta": "53",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Twilight",
      "pregunta": "54",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "batman",
      "pregunta": "55",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "king kong",
      "pregunta": "56",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "bee movie",
      "pregunta": "57",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Stand by Me",
      "pregunta": "58",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "titanic",
      "pregunta": "59",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "it",
      "pregunta": "60",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "babe",
      "pregunta": "61",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "snatch",
      "pregunta": "62",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "the Polar|Express",
      "pregunta": "63",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Flight",
      "pregunta": "64",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Night at|the Museum",
      "pregunta": "65",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Sex and|the City",
      "pregunta": "66",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "turbo",
      "pregunta": "67",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Zootopia",
      "pregunta": "68",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "The|Godfather",
      "pregunta": "69",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Teenage Mutant|Ninja Turtles",
      "pregunta": "70",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "rocky",
      "pregunta": "71",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "creed",
      "pregunta": "72",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Edward|Scissorhands",
      "pregunta": "73",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Back to|the Future",
      "pregunta": "74",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Braveheart",
      "pregunta": "75",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "The X Files",
      "pregunta": "76",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "dumbo",
      "pregunta": "77",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "The Italian|Job",
      "pregunta": "78",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Hachi|A Dogs Tale",
      "pregunta": "79",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "A Bugs|Life",
      "pregunta": "80",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Nine|Queens",
      "pregunta": "81",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "The Hangover",
      "pregunta": "82",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "101|Dalmatians",
      "pregunta": "83",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "happy feet",
      "pregunta": "84",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "space jam",
      "pregunta": "85",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Midnight|in Paris",
      "pregunta": "86",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "the 33",
      "pregunta": "87",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "scream",
      "pregunta": "88",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Singing in|the Rain",
      "pregunta": "89",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "ted",
      "pregunta": "90",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "The Sixth|Sense",
      "pregunta": "91",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "The Curious Case|of Benjamin Button",
      "pregunta": "92",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "top gun",
      "pregunta": "93",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "You have|Got Mail",
      "pregunta": "94",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "invictus",
      "pregunta": "95",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "wimbledon",
      "pregunta": "96",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Black Hawk|down",
      "pregunta": "97",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "The Da|Vinci Code",
      "pregunta": "98",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "A Clockwork|Orange",
      "pregunta": "99",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "thor",
      "pregunta": "100",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Air Force|One",
      "pregunta": "101",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "The Phantom|of the Opera",
      "pregunta": "102",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Runaway|Bride",
      "pregunta": "103",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Alice in|Wonderland",
      "pregunta": "104",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "frozen",
      "pregunta": "105",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "The Jungle|Book",
      "pregunta": "106",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "the karate|kid",
      "pregunta": "107",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Paranormal|Activity",
      "pregunta": "108",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "The Exorcist",
      "pregunta": "109",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "The Smurfs",
      "pregunta": "110",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "cobra",
      "pregunta": "111",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "the matrix",
      "pregunta": "112",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "twister",
      "pregunta": "113",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "National|Treasure",
      "pregunta": "114",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "The Notebook",
      "pregunta": "115",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Gone in|60 Seconds",
      "pregunta": "116",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "super 8",
      "pregunta": "117",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Cool|Runnings",
      "pregunta": "118",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "The Little|Mermaid",
      "pregunta": "119",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "World War Z",
      "pregunta": "120",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "dracula",
      "pregunta": "121",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "aladdin",
      "pregunta": "122",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "toy story",
      "pregunta": "123",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "jurassic|park",
      "pregunta": "124",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "super|size me",
      "pregunta": "125",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Patriots|Day",
      "pregunta": "126",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "Cast Away",
      "pregunta": "127",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "godzilla",
      "pregunta": "128",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Movies with emojis",
      "respuesta": "The Lake|House",
      "pregunta": "129",
      "categoria": "Emojis"
    }
  ]
}
